[{"id":123,"question":"What does HTML stand for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Hyper Text Markup Language","answer_b":"Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language","answer_c":"Home Tool Markup Language","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":124,"question":"Who is making the Web standards?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The World Wide Web Consortium","answer_b":"Google","answer_c":"Mozilla","answer_d":"Microsoft","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":125,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<heading>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<h6>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":126,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<break>","answer_b":"<br>","answer_c":"<lb>","answer_d":"<bl>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":127,"question":"What is the correct HTML for adding a background color?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<body bg=\"yellow\">","answer_b":"<background>yellow</background>","answer_c":"<body style=\"background-color:yellow;\">","answer_d":"<body style bg=\"yellow\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":128,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element to define important text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<b>","answer_b":"<i>","answer_c":"<important>","answer_d":"<strong>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":129,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element to define emphasized text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<i>","answer_b":"<em>","answer_c":"<italic>","answer_d":"<it>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":130,"question":"What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<a url=\"http://www.w3schools.com\">W3Schools.com</a>","answer_b":"<a name=\"http://www.w3schools.com\">W3Schools.com</a>","answer_c":"<a>http://www.w3schools.com</a>","answer_d":"<a href=\"http://www.w3schools.com\">W3Schools</a>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":131,"question":"Which character is used to indicate an end tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"/","answer_b":"<","answer_c":"*","answer_d":"^","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":132,"question":"How can you open a link in a new tab/browser window?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<a href=\"url\" target=\"new\">","answer_b":"<a href=\"url\" new>","answer_c":"<a href=\"url\" target=\"_blank\">","answer_d":"<a href=\"url\" target=\"new-tab\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":133,"question":"Which of these elements are all <table> elements?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<table><head><tfoot>","answer_b":"<thead><body><tr>","answer_c":"<table><tr><td>","answer_d":"<table><tr><tt>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":134,"question":"Inline elements are normally displayed without starting a new line","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":135,"question":"How can you make a numbered list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<ol>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<list>","answer_d":"<ul>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":136,"question":"How can you make a bulleted list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<ol>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<ul>","answer_d":"<list>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":137,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a checkbox?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"checkbox\">","answer_b":"<input type=\"check\">","answer_c":"<check>","answer_d":"<checkbox>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":138,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a text input field?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<textinput type=\"text\">","answer_b":"<input type=\"text\">","answer_c":"<input type=\"textfield\">","answer_d":"<textfield>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":139,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a drop-down list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"dropdown\">","answer_b":"<input type=\"list\">","answer_c":"<select>","answer_d":"<list>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":140,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a text area?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"textbox\">","answer_b":"<textarea>","answer_c":"<input type=\"textarea\">","answer_d":"<textbox>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":141,"question":"What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<img src=\"image.gif\" alt=\"MyImage\">","answer_b":"<img alt=\"MyImage\">image.gif</img>","answer_c":"<img href=\"image.gif\" alt=\"MyImage\">","answer_d":"<image src=\"image.gif\" alt=\"MyImage\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":142,"question":"What is the correct HTML for inserting a background image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<background img=\"background.gif\">","answer_b":"<body bg=\"background.gif\">","answer_c":"<body style=\"background-image:url(background.gif)\">","answer_d":"<background style img=\"background.gif\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":143,"question":"An <iframe> is used to display a web page within a web page.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":144,"question":"HTML comments start with <!-- and end with -->","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":145,"question":"Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":146,"question":"Which HTML element defines the title of a document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<title>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<meta>","answer_d":"<start>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":147,"question":"Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"alt","answer_b":"title","answer_c":"longdesc","answer_d":"src","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":148,"question":"Which doctype is correct for HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<!DOCTYPE HTML5>","answer_b":"<!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC>","answer_c":"<!DOCTYPE html>","answer_d":"<HTML5>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":149,"question":"Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<footer>","answer_b":"<section>","answer_c":"<bottom>","answer_d":"<down>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":150,"question":"In HTML, you can embed SVG elements directly into an HTML page","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":151,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<movie>","answer_b":"<media>","answer_c":"<type=\"video\">","answer_d":"<video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":152,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for playing audio files?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<audio>","answer_b":"<sound>","answer_c":"<mp3>","answer_d":"<type \"mpr3\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":153,"question":"The HTML global attribute, \"contenteditable\" is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specify whether the content of an element should be editable or not","answer_b":"Update content from the server","answer_c":"Specifies a context menu for an element. The menu appears when a user right-clicks on the element","answer_d":"Return the position of the first found occurrence of content inside a string","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":154,"question":"In HTML, onblur and onfocus are:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Style attributes","answer_b":"HTML elements","answer_c":"Event attributes","answer_d":"Text styles","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":155,"question":"Graphics defined by SVG is in which format?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CSS","answer_b":"XML","answer_c":"HTML","answer_d":"JSON","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":156,"question":"The HTML <canvas> element is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"draw graphics","answer_b":"display database records","answer_c":"create draggable elements","answer_d":"manipulate data in MySQL","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":157,"question":"In HTML, which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"formvalidate","answer_b":"placeholder","answer_c":"validate","answer_d":"required","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":158,"question":"Which input type defines a slider control?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"slider","answer_b":"search","answer_c":"range","answer_d":"controls","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":159,"question":"Which HTML element is used to display a scalar measurement within a range?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<range>","answer_b":"<gauge>","answer_c":"<meter>","answer_d":"<measure>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":160,"question":"Which HTML element defines navigation links?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<nav>","answer_b":"<navigate>","answer_c":"<navigation>","answer_d":"<navlink>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":161,"question":"In HTML, what does the <aside> element define?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The ASCII character-set; to send information between computers on the Internet","answer_b":"A navigation list to be shown at the left side of the page","answer_c":"A list to be included in a certain part of the page","answer_d":"Content aside from the page content","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":162,"question":"Which HTML element is used to specify a header for a document or section?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<top>","answer_b":"<header>","answer_c":"<head>","answer_d":"<section>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":205,"question":"Which operator is included in the data manipulation language (DML)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"INSERT","answer_b":"GRANT","answer_c":"CREATE","answer_d":"DROP","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":206,"question":"SQL (Structured Query Language) is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"imperative programming language","answer_b":"the language of structured queries","answer_c":"the language of queries by pattern","answer_d":"DBMS (DataBase Management System)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":207,"question":"DISTINCT keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"There is no such keyword","answer_b":"For selecting only unique records by a specific field","answer_c":"To reduce the load on the server with loss of query performance","answer_d":"To speed up the selection for a specific field","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":208,"question":"INSERT keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"adding data","answer_b":"manage users","answer_c":"to select data","answer_d":"to change data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":209,"question":"UPDATE keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"to create database elements","answer_b":"to change data","answer_c":"to manage users","answer_d":"to select data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":211,"question":"You have to sort records in the descending order by field \"rating\". Which query will be correct?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SORT BY \"rating\" DESC","answer_b":"SORT BY \"rating\"","answer_c":"ORDER BY \"rating\" DESC","answer_d":"ORDER BY \"rating\"","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":212,"question":"Which operator is not included in the data manipulation language (DML)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UPDATE","answer_b":"DELETE","answer_c":"CREATE","answer_d":"SELECT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":213,"question":"Words ORDER BY in the SQL operator","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"eliminates all repeated rows from the result set","answer_b":"allows you to combine the results of individual queries across multiple tables into a single result table","answer_c":"converts the value of a column or function to a different type","answer_d":"changes the order of output rows","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":214,"question":"What does the WHERE SQL operator does:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"restricts the set of rows to the selection of those records for which the condition is true","answer_b":"converts the value of a column or function to a different type","answer_c":"changes the order of output rows","answer_d":"eliminates all row repeats from the result set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":215,"question":"Which command is used to modify column names or table structure?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"MODIFY","answer_b":"ADD","answer_c":"CHANGE","answer_d":"ALTER","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":216,"question":"Which is the right syntax for the DISTINCT SQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT DIFFERENT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_b":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 WHERE table;","answer_c":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":217,"question":"What is the use of SQL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Storing data in database","answer_b":"Manipulating data in database","answer_c":"Retrieving data in database","answer_d":"Displaying images","answer_e":"Managing queries","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":218,"question":"Which SQL statement is used to return only different values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DUPLICATE","answer_b":"DISTINCT","answer_c":"DIFFERENT","answer_d":"SELECT","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":219,"question":"What does SQL stands for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Structure query language","answer_b":"Strong question language","answer_c":"Structured question language","answer_d":"Separate query language","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":220,"question":"Which keyword is used with the ALTER command to delete a column?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DROP","answer_b":"DELETE","answer_c":"REMOVE","answer_d":"CHANGE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":221,"question":"The command to remove rows from a table \"MOVIE\" is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REMOVE FROM MOVIE","answer_b":"DROP FROM MOVIE","answer_c":"DELETE FROM MOVIE WHERE","answer_d":"UPDATE FROM MOVIE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":223,"question":"Which keyword is used with the UPDATE command to change the value?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE","answer_b":"MODIFY","answer_c":"ADD","answer_d":"SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":224,"question":"Which command is used to specify the number of records to return?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT","answer_b":"SELECT TOP","answer_c":"EXTRACT","answer_d":"SELECT SPECIFIC","answer_e":"LIMIT","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":225,"question":"Which command is used to insert a new records in the table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ADD","answer_b":"INSERT INTO","answer_c":"INSERT","answer_d":"NEW","answer_e":"CREATE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":226,"question":"You can add a row using SQL in a database with which of the following?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ADD","answer_b":"CREATE","answer_c":"INSERT","answer_d":"MAKE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":227,"question":"Which SQL statement is used to extract data from the database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT","answer_b":"ACCESS","answer_c":"OPEN","answer_d":"GET","answer_e":"ACQUIRE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":228,"question":"The SQL WHERE clause?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Limits the column data that are returned","answer_b":"Limits the row data are returned","answer_c":"Both A and B are correct","answer_d":"Neither A nor B are correct","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":231,"question":"Which of the following SQL statements is correct?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT cname, COUNT(cname) FROM Orders","answer_b":"SELECT cname, COUNT(cname) FROM Orders GROUP BY cname","answer_c":"SELECT cname, COUNT(cname) FROM Orders ORDER BY cname","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":232,"question":"Which of the following statements are true about SQL injection attacks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Wrapping all variables containing user input by a call to mysql_real_escape_string() makes the code immune to SQL injections.","answer_b":"Parametrized queries do not make code less vulnearable to SQL injections.","answer_c":"SQL injections are not possible, if only emulated prepared statements are used.","answer_d":"Usage of later versions of MySQL, validation, and explicit setting of the charset of user input are valid measures to decrease vulnerability to SQL injections.","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":234,"question":"Can you insert multiple rows with only one INSERT query?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"It's possible but only with newer MySQL versions","answer_d":"Yes but these inserts cause data corruption","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":235,"question":"Which arithmetic operator you can not use?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"+","answer_b":"-","answer_c":"*","answer_d":"\\","answer_e":"%","answer_f":"All are valid"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":238,"question":"Which of the following is the best MySQL data type for currency values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SMALLINT","answer_b":"DECIMAL(18,4)","answer_c":"VARCHAR(32)","answer_d":"BIGINT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":241,"question":"Can you start two MySQL servers at one PC?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":244,"question":"What is the default DATE field type format?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DD-MM-YYYY","answer_b":"YYYY-DD-MM","answer_c":"YYYY-MM-DD","answer_d":"MM-DD-YY","answer_e":"MMDDYYYY","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":246,"question":"What is the name of the utility used to extract NDB configuration information?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ndb_config","answer_b":"cluster_config","answer_c":"ndb --config","answer_d":"configNdb","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":248,"question":"Which of the following will raise MySQL's version of an error?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SIGNAL","answer_b":"RAISE","answer_c":"ERROR","answer_d":"None of these","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":249,"question":"Which query will return values containing strings \"apple\", \"banana\" or \"orange\" in the database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT * FROM table WHERE field REGEXP ‘apple|banana|orange’;","answer_b":"SELECT * FROM table WHERE field LIKE ‘%apple%’ OR field LIKE ‘%banana%’ OR field LIKE ‘%orange%’;","answer_c":"SELECT * FROM table WHERE field = ‘%apple%’ OR field = ‘%banana%’ OR field = ‘%orange%’;","answer_d":"SELECT * FROM table WHERE field = ‘?apple?’ OR field = ‘?banana?’ OR field = ‘?orange?’;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":250,"question":"Which type you will select if you need to store binary data?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BLOB","answer_b":"BIGINT","answer_c":"INT","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":"Both BIGINT and INT","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":251,"question":"Which of the following will reset the MySQL password for a particular user?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=’password’ WHERE User=’username’;","answer_b":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=PASSWORD(‘password’) WHERE User=’username’;","answer_c":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=RESET(‘password’) WHERE User=’username’;","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":253,"question":"How to dump the whole MySQL database to a file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mysql -e \"select * from table\" -u user -pxxxxxxx database > dumpfile.txt","answer_b":"mysql -e \"select * from table\" database > dumpfile.txt","answer_c":"SELECT * from table FIELDS TERMINATED BY ',' ENCLOSED BY \"\" LINES TERMINATED BY 'n'","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":325,"question":"What will happen if two tables have names 'users' and 'USERS'?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"This is not possible because table names are case insensitive","answer_b":"This depends on lower_case_table_names system variable","answer_c":"This is possible only on UNIX/LINUX","answer_d":"This is possible only on Windows","answer_e":"This is possible because table names are case sensitive","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":326,"question":"Which of the queries below will return 0 (false)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT \"EXPERTRATING\" LIKE \"EXP%\"","answer_b":"SELECT \"EXPERTRATING\" LIKE \"Exp%\"","answer_c":"SELECT BINARY \"EXPERTRATING\" LIKE \"EXP%\"","answer_d":"SELECT BINARY \"EXPERTRATING\" LIKE \"Exp%\"","answer_e":"All those will return 1 (true)","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":328,"question":"Which of the following statements are true?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_b":"Alias names can be up to 255 characters in length","answer_c":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 256 characters in length","answer_d":"Alias names can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":329,"question":"How can you change table sctructure after it was created?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE TABLE","answer_b":"MODIFY TABLE","answer_c":"ALTER TABLE","answer_d":"UPDATE TABLE","answer_e":"It's not possible to change the structure","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":330,"question":"Which is not a  valid bit operator?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"&&","answer_c":"<<","answer_d":"|","answer_e":">>","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":331,"question":"What is the best advantage of InnoDB over MyISAM?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"InnoDB is thread safe","answer_b":"InnoDB provides a transaction safe environment","answer_c":"InnoDB can handle table with more than 1000 columns","answer_d":"InnoDB provides FULLTEXT indexes","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":"All of the above"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":332,"question":"What will happen if some of the columns in a table are of char datatype and others are of varchar datatype?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Nothing will happen","answer_b":"MySQL will generate an error","answer_c":"MySQL will convert all varchar datatypes into char","answer_d":"MySQL will convert all char datatypes into varchar","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":333,"question":"If you insert (00) as the value of the year in a date column, what will be stored in the database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"0000","answer_b":"1900","answer_c":"2000","answer_d":"Cannot be determined","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":334,"question":"Which of the following is not a valid logical operator?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"&&","answer_c":"AND","answer_d":"!","answer_e":"NOT","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":338,"question":"What is the maximum size of a row in a MyISAM table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"No limit","answer_b":"OS specific","answer_c":"65534","answer_d":"128","answer_e":"2’147’483’648","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":339,"question":"Which of the following are not Numeric column types?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BIGINT","answer_b":"LARGEINT","answer_c":"SMALLINT","answer_d":"DOUBLE","answer_e":"DECIMAL","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":344,"question":"A systematic collection of data stored in a central location is known as?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CSV","answer_b":"Flat file","answer_c":"Database","answer_d":"Excel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":345,"question":"Which type of database management system represents relations using tables?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Network DBMS","answer_b":"Hierachical DBMS","answer_c":"Relational DBMS","answer_d":"Object Oriented DBMS","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":346,"question":"MySQL supports multiple database storage engines.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":347,"question":"MySQL workbench decreases the productivity of a MySQL developer compared to other server access tools such as phpMyAdmin?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":348,"question":"The logic model of a database is?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"concerned with the planning of the entire database development life cycle","answer_b":"concerned with the physical implementation of the database","answer_c":"concerned with developing the database model taking into consideration the physical implementation","answer_d":"concerned with developing the database model without taking into consideration the physical implementation or the DBMS","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":349,"question":"The database development lifecycle is very important to the successful implementation of a database system.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":350,"question":"Normalizations is...","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"concerned with the physical implementation of the database","answer_b":"a database design technique that encourages storing data in multiple databases","answer_c":"a database design technique that eliminates relationships from a database","answer_d":"a database design technique used to minimize data redundancy and duplication","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":351,"question":"What is a composite key?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"its is a key that is defined as the primary key in another table","answer_b":"it is a key that uniquely identifies a record in a database","answer_c":"its is an optional key and allows null values","answer_d":"it is a primary key that consists of more than one field that uniquely identifies a record","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":352,"question":"Which of the following IS NOT true regarding ER modeling","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ER models can be converted into a database","answer_b":"ER models waste the database developer's time","answer_c":"ER models increase the database developer's productivity","answer_d":"ER models act as non technical communication tools","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":353,"question":"A one to many relationship can only contain multiple entries of both primary and foreign keys.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":355,"question":"The command DROP SCHEMA `STUDENTS`; will delete the students database.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":356,"question":"The WHERE clause is mandatory when using the SELECT command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":357,"question":"Which of the following scripts will run successfully","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Users statistics SELECT customer name FROM customers;","answer_b":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;","answer_c":"SELECT FROM `customers` 'customer name';","answer_d":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers ORDER BY zone WHERE cat_id = 12;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":359,"question":"What will be the output of the following query. SELECT * FROM `sales` WHERE amount > 200.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts starting from 200 and above","answer_b":"the query will output sales records with the amount equal to 200.","answer_c":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts less than 200","answer_d":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts greater than 200","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":360,"question":"The query SELECT * FROM `movies` INSERT INTO `movies_archive`  will be executed without any errors.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":361,"question":"What will be the output of the following query INSERT INTO students (student name) VALUE ('James Lenon');","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"a student record with the name James Lenon will be added into the students table","answer_b":"the above query will generate an error message.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":362,"question":"What command is used to permanently remove a record from a database table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DROP","answer_b":"REMOVE","answer_c":"DELETE","answer_d":"CUT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":363,"question":"What improvements can be made to the query UPDATE students SET `contact number` = 0999;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The query does not need any improvements","answer_b":"enclose the contact number in single quotes","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":364,"question":"The clause ORDER is used to sort records in either ascending or descending order.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":365,"question":"The ASC and DESC keywords can be used in the same statement","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":366,"question":"The GROUP BY command cannot be used with aggregate functions together","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":367,"question":"Wildcards are","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"not supported by MySQL","answer_b":"characters such as % which perform single character matching","answer_c":"characters such as $ which perform pattern matches","answer_d":"used to perform pattern matches","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":368,"question":"MySQL supports user defined functions","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":370,"question":"What will be the output of the query SELECT MINIMUM (amount) FROM sales;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"return the lowest sales value","answer_b":"the query will generate an error","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":372,"question":"What will be the output of the SELECT CASE WHEN NULL = NULL THEN 'YES' ELSE 'NO' END","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"An Error will be generated","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":373,"question":"MySQL does not support auto generating numbers","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":374,"question":"What will be the effect of inserting 500 rows in a table with the following definition. CREATE TABLE `categories` ( `category_id` tinyint(3) AUTO_INCREMENT, `category_name` varchar(150) DEFAULT NULL, `remarks` varchar(500) DEFAULT NULL, PRIMARY KEY","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"500 rows will be inserted into the table","answer_b":"only 100 rows will be inserted","answer_c":"a table with the above definition is not possible","answer_d":"half the records will be inserted then an error will be generated","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":375,"question":"Once a table has been created in MySQL, its structure cannot be altered","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":376,"question":"The syntax for adding a new column to an existing table is ALTER TABLE `table_name` ADD COLUMN `column_name` `data_type`;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":377,"question":"The employees table has 20 records, what will be the output of the query SELECT gender FROM employees GROUP BY gender;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will return two rows only","answer_b":"the query will not return any records","answer_c":"the query will return 20 records","answer_d":"the query will generate an error message","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":378,"question":"What will be the effect of the query SELECT TOP (100) FROM customers when executed against MySQL database.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The query will return 100 records from the database table sorted in descending order","answer_b":"The query will return all records from the database table","answer_c":"The query will generate an error","answer_d":"The query will return 100 records from the database table sorted in ascending order","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":379,"question":"What will be the output of the query SELECT * FROM `members` LIMIT 1, 2;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will generate an error","answer_b":"the query will return all records from the members table","answer_c":"the query will return the first 2 records","answer_d":"the query will return skip the first record then return the following 2 records only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":380,"question":"The query SELECT name, (SELECT study_program FROM programs) study_program FROM students will return the student name and the program that the student is studying.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":381,"question":"Sub queries have better performance compared to JOIN queries","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":382,"question":"The UNION command is used to combine result sets from more than one query into a single result set","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":383,"question":"What will be the effect of the query SELECT c.*,e.* FROM clients c INNER JOIN employees e ON c.emp_no = e.emp_no;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"return all the records from the clients table and only those that match the emp_no from the employees table","answer_b":"The query will generate an error","answer_c":"return all the records from the employees table and only those that match the emp_no from the clients table","answer_d":"return only records that have matching emp_no values in both tables","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":384,"question":"Which program copies databases from one server to another?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Mysqlcopydb","answer_b":"Mysqldbflush","answer_c":"Mysqlflushdb","answer_d":"Mysqldbcopy","answer_e":"Mysqlmovedb","answer_f":"Mysqldbmove"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":385,"question":"To use 'mysqldbcopy' which privileges are required on the source server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CREATE","answer_b":"UPDATE","answer_c":"SELECT","answer_d":"INSERT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":386,"question":"The Function 'fetchrow_hashref()' returns reference to hash row values keyed by ______________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Row Name","answer_b":"Database Name","answer_c":"Table Name","answer_d":"Column Name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"},{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":388,"question":"Which is the log in which data changes received from a replication master server are written?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Error Log","answer_b":"Relay Log","answer_c":"General Query Log","answer_d":"Binary Log","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":389,"question":"The maximum length of the char columns is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"65, 535 Bytes","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"255 Bytes","answer_d":"256 Bytes","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":390,"question":"MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SHOW;  ;","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"CHARACTER SET;","answer_d":"SHOW CHARACTER SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":391,"question":"Which one is the correct declaration for choosing the 'Character Set' other than default?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Varchar(20);","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"Varchar(20) Character Set;","answer_d":"Varchar(20) Character Set Utf8;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":393,"question":"The \"father\" Of MySQL Is ______.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Bill Joy","answer_b":"Stephanie Wall","answer_c":"Bill Gates","answer_d":"Michael Widenius","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":394,"question":"To use MySQL on your computer, you'll need","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Perl, PHP Or Java","answer_b":"FTP And Telnet","answer_c":"Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases","answer_d":"A Browser","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":395,"question":"The main MySQL program that does all the data handling is called","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Mysql","answer_b":"Mysqld","answer_c":"Httpd","answer_d":"Mysql.exe","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":397,"question":"Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"English","answer_b":"The Structured Query Language","answer_c":"Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages","answer_d":"Swedish","answer_e":"Binary","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":399,"question":"Which of the following is NOT supported by MySQL","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Temporary (Hash) Tables","answer_b":"Stored Procedures","answer_c":"Regular Expression Matching","answer_d":"Table Joining","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":400,"question":"One of the early proponents of a Relational Database who laid down many of the principles we use to this day was:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Xigang Koi","answer_b":"Mahatma Coate","answer_c":"William Crawford","answer_d":"Edgar Codd","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":401,"question":"Which of these is a valid call to a function (watch The Spaces Carefully!)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CONCAT( A , B )","answer_b":"CONCAT( \"A\" . \"B\" )","answer_c":"CONCAT ( \"A\" , \"B\" )","answer_d":"CONCAT ( A , B )","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":402,"question":"If you want to undo a GRANT, you should use","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REVOKE","answer_b":"UNGRANT","answer_c":"UNDO","answer_d":"DELETE","answer_e":"REMOVE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":403,"question":"How many distinct, different values can you hold in an Enum field?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"255","answer_b":"2 (True And False)","answer_c":"65535","answer_d":"7","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":404,"question":"Which of the following is NOT available in MySQL:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REVOKE","answer_b":"JOIN","answer_c":"LIKE","answer_d":"FETCH","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":405,"question":"The program called MySQL is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"There Isn't A Program Just Called Mysql","answer_b":"A Client Program That Lets You Send SQL Commands To The Database Engine","answer_c":"The Database Engine","answer_d":"A Wrapper Through Which Java Clients Must Connect To The Databases  The Database Engine","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":406,"question":"In a LIKE clause, you can ask for any 6 Letter Value by writing:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"LIKE .{6}","answer_b":"LIKE ??????","answer_c":"LIKE ^.{6}$","answer_d":"LIKE ______ (Six Underscore Characters)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":407,"question":"Which of the following is available in MySQL:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CREATE VIEW","answer_b":"CREATE DATABASE","answer_c":"CREATE TRIGGER","answer_d":"CREATE SCHEMA","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":408,"question":"Which of these is not a valid name for a column","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To","answer_b":"Near","answer_c":"Far","answer_d":"From","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":409,"question":"Which statement is used to insert a new data in a database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"INSERT NEW","answer_b":"UPDATE","answer_c":"INSERT INTO","answer_d":"Add New","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":411,"question":"Which of the following is an aggregate function in MySQL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"LIKE","answer_b":"MAX","answer_c":"Group By","answer_d":"Union","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":412,"question":"Which command is used to remove all rows from a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Delete","answer_b":"Both Delete and Remove","answer_c":"Truncate","answer_d":"Remove","answer_e":"Drop","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":414,"question":"Character data can be stored as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Both fixed or variable length strings","answer_b":"Variable length strings","answer_c":"Fixed length strings","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":415,"question":"Which declaration doesn't use the same number of bytes and consumption of bytes depending on the input data?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Varchar","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"Char","answer_d":"Both Varchar And Char","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":416,"question":"The maximum length of the varchar columns Is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Upto 65, 535 Bytes","answer_b":"Upto 65, 567 Bytes","answer_c":"Upto 256 Bytes","answer_d":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":417,"question":"Which \"text Type\" has the maximum number of bytes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Long Text","answer_b":"Text","answer_c":"Tiny Text","answer_d":"Medium Text","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":418,"question":"MySQL comes with a standard client libraries for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"C Only","answer_b":"PHP And C","answer_c":"Perl,  Java And C","answer_d":"Java Only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":420,"question":"What Is a MySQL View?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"VIEWS are virtual tables that do not store any data of their own but display data stored in other tables.","answer_b":"VIEWS are static tables that store data but the data can't be changed","answer_c":"VIEWS are temporary tables that store data which store data only for a certain amount of time","answer_d":"VIEWS are no different that any other tables except they are used for faster loading.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":422,"question":"Is the NULL value treated as 0?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":423,"question":"Which function is used to get the current time in mysql?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"getTime()","answer_b":"NOW()","answer_c":"Time()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":424,"question":"DCL is used for _______?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Managing the changes made by DML statements","answer_b":"Inserting, Deleting and Updating data","answer_c":"Control access to data stored in a database","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":425,"question":"TCL is used for _______?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Control access to data stored in a database","answer_b":"Managing the changes made by DML statements","answer_c":"Defining database schema","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":427,"question":"What is Granularity?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The size of data items","answer_b":"The size of database","answer_c":"The size of file","answer_d":"The size of record","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":428,"question":"Which level of Abstraction describes what data are stored in the Database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Physical Level","answer_b":"Logical Level","answer_c":"Abstraction Level","answer_d":"View Level","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":429,"question":"The problem that occurs when one transaction updates a database item and then the transaction fails for some reason is ________.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Dirty Read Problem","answer_b":"Temporary Modify Problem","answer_c":"Temporary Select Problem","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":430,"question":"Data Warehouse provides","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Transaction Responsiveness","answer_b":"Demand and Supply Responsiveness","answer_c":"Storage, Functionality Responsiveness to queries","answer_d":"None of these","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":431,"question":"Which of the following is true?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A relation in BCNF is always in 3NF","answer_b":"BCNF and 3NF are same.","answer_c":"A relation in BCNF is not in 3NF.","answer_d":"A relation in 3NF is always in BCNF.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":432,"question":"Referential integrity is directly related to","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Relation Key","answer_b":"Foreign Key","answer_c":"Unique Key","answer_d":"Primary Key","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":433,"question":"_____ is process of extracting previously non known valid and actionable information from large data to make crucial business and strategic decisions.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Data Management","answer_b":"Meta Data","answer_c":"Data Mining","answer_d":"Database","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":434,"question":"Which of the following statements is NOT true for views in SQL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Select statement used in the view definition cannot include ORDER BY clause.","answer_b":"A view contains a copy of the data","answer_c":"A view drives its data from the base tables(s)","answer_d":"A view is updatable if it has been defined from a single relation","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":435,"question":"In order to add a new column to an existing table in SQL, which command do we need to use?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"MODIFY TABLE","answer_b":"ALTER COLUMNS","answer_c":"ALTER TABLE","answer_d":"EDIT TABLE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":437,"question":"What is called if a value shouldn't be greater than 100?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Integrity constraint","answer_b":"Feasible constraint","answer_c":"Over-defined constraint","answer_d":"Referential constraint","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":438,"question":"The data type BLOB stands for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Binary Large Object","answer_b":"Big List Object","answer_c":"Binary List Object","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":"Binary List Obsolete Object","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":439,"question":"Function which causes retrieval of any kind of data from database is considered as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Interface or Signature","answer_b":"Logical signature","answer_c":"Conceptual signature","answer_d":"User friendly signature","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":441,"question":"A table that displays data redundancies yields ________ anomalies","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Insertion","answer_b":"All of options","answer_c":"Update","answer_d":"Deletion","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":442,"question":"MVD is known as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Many Value Dependency","answer_b":"More Value Dependency","answer_c":"Multi Value Dependency","answer_d":"All of the Above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":443,"question":"What is the HTML Tag for the largest heading","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<h6>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<heading>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":444,"question":"Which of following is not an attribute of <form> tag","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Action","answer_b":"url","answer_c":"name","answer_d":"Method","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":445,"question":"HTML Is a subset of","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SGMT","answer_b":"None Of These","answer_c":"SGML","answer_d":"SGMD","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":446,"question":"All HTML Tags must be enclosed In?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"? And !","answer_b":"# And #","answer_c":"{ And }","answer_d":"< And >","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":447,"question":"The BODY Tag is usually used after","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"EM Tag","answer_b":"HEAD Tag","answer_c":"HTML Tag","answer_d":"TITLE Tag","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":448,"question":"Choose the correct HTML Tag to make a text Italic","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<italic>","answer_b":"<il>","answer_c":"<i>","answer_d":"<it>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":449,"question":"A much better approach to establish the base URL is to use the ______ element.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BODY","answer_b":"HEAD","answer_c":"BASE","answer_d":"None Of The Above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":450,"question":"Gif and Jpg are the two main types of what ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Videos","answer_b":"Animated Effects","answer_c":"Images","answer_d":"None Of The Above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":451,"question":"To start a list using circles, use","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<ul Type=\"circle\">","answer_b":"<ul =\"round\">","answer_c":"<ul \"round\">","answer_d":"<ul Type=\"round\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":452,"question":"Which Is not a property of attribute behaviour of <Marquee> Tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Blur","answer_b":"Slide","answer_c":"Alternate","answer_d":"Scroll","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":453,"question":"A simple text file which tells the browser what to cache Is known as a/an ________.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Input Files","answer_b":"HTML File","answer_c":"A Manifest File","answer_d":"Output Files","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":454,"question":"Which HTML Tag is used to define a client - side script such as the Javascript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<unscript>","answer_b":"None Of The Above","answer_c":"Both Above","answer_d":"<script>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":455,"question":"Which tag is used to create a checkbox in HTML?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<checkbox>","answer_b":"< Input type = \"checkbox\">","answer_c":"<cb>","answer_d":"< Input type  \"checkbox\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":456,"question":"Which attribute sets the text direction as related to lang attribute.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Sub","answer_b":"Dir","answer_c":"Ds","answer_d":"Lang","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":457,"question":"Which html attribute is used to provide an advisory text about an element or Its contents.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Dir","answer_b":"Title","answer_c":"Tooltip","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":458,"question":"Which оf the following class centers tabs/pills?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":".nav-justified","answer_b":".nav.navbar-nav","answer_c":".nav Nav-pills","answer_d":".nav-stacked","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":459,"question":"Which of the following will create the so called Hamburger Menu?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Icon-prev","answer_b":"Icon-next","answer_c":"Img-circle","answer_d":"Icon-bar","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":460,"question":"Which of the following is for title of the modal?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Modal-title","answer_b":"Modal-sm","answer_c":"Modal-lg","answer_d":"Modal-open","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":461,"question":"Which of the following aligns media objects?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Media","answer_b":"Medibody","answer_c":"Mediobject","answer_d":"Medilist","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":462,"question":"Which of the following adds a checkmark Icon inside an Input?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Help-block","answer_b":"Has-warning","answer_c":"Has-feedback","answer_d":"Has-success","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":463,"question":"Which Tag is used if you want to indicate the importance of the phrase?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<h1>","answer_b":"<h2>","answer_c":"<strong>","answer_d":"<em>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":464,"question":"__________ is the XML equivalent to strict HTML 4.01.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"XHTML 1.0 Frameset","answer_b":"XHTML 1.0 Transitional","answer_c":"XHTML 1.0 Strict","answer_d":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":465,"question":"Which of the following encoding an XML parser assumes ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UTF-16","answer_b":"UTF-32","answer_c":"UTF-8","answer_d":"UTF-64","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":466,"question":"Which of the following will provide additional Information about something?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Jumbotron","answer_b":"Item","answer_c":"Label-danger","answer_d":"Label","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":467,"question":"What type of a language is HTML?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Scripting Language","answer_b":"Markup Language","answer_c":"Programming Language","answer_d":"Network Protocol","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":468,"question":"All elements are identified by their __________ and are marked up using either start tags and end tags or self-closing tags","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Attribute Names","answer_b":"Tag Names","answer_c":"Class Names","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":469,"question":"The __________ Element represents a span of text that is isolated from it's surroundings for the purposes of bidirectional text formatting","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"B","answer_b":"Base","answer_c":"Bdo","answer_d":"Bdi","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":471,"question":"Apart from the <b> tag, what other Tag makes text bold ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<emp>","answer_b":"<strong>","answer_c":"<fat>","answer_d":"<black>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":472,"question":"Who is known as the father of world wide web (WWW)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Robert Cailliau","answer_b":"Charles Darwin","answer_c":"Tim Thompson","answer_d":"Tim Berners-Lee","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":474,"question":"What type of join is needed when you wish to return rows that have matching values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Equi-join","answer_b":"All of the mentioned.","answer_c":"Outer join","answer_d":"Natural join","answer_e":"None of the mentioned.","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":475,"question":"How can you make A bulleted list with numbers?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<dl>","answer_b":"<ul>","answer_c":"<ol>","answer_d":"<list>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":476,"question":"What should be the first tag in any HTML Document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>","answer_b":"<!doctype html>","answer_c":"<title>","answer_d":"<head>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":477,"question":"What tag is used to display a picture in a HTML page?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Picture","answer_b":"Image","answer_c":"Src","answer_d":"Img","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":478,"question":"HTML are web pages read and rendered by","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Compiler","answer_b":"Interpreter","answer_c":"Web Browser","answer_d":"Server","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":479,"question":"HTML tags are surrounded by which type of brackets.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Curly","answer_b":"Angle","answer_c":"Squart","answer_d":"Round","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":480,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when an element gets user Input?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ondata","answer_b":"Onloadeddata","answer_c":"Oninput","answer_d":"Onhaschange","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":481,"question":"Intensity of a color can be described through","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Hue","answer_b":"Grayscale","answer_c":"Lightness","answer_d":"Saturation","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":482,"question":"How can you create an E-mail link?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<a Href=\"a@b\">","answer_b":"<mail Href=\"a@b\">","answer_c":"<a Href=\"mailto:a@b.com\">","answer_d":"<mail>a@b</mail>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":483,"question":"What is the correct HTML tag for inserting a line break?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<break />","answer_b":"<nbsp>","answer_c":"<lb />","answer_d":"<br />","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":484,"question":"Which are the objects used for storing data on the client provided by the HTML local storage?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Window.localStorage","answer_b":"Window.sessionStorage","answer_c":"Window.localSession","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":485,"question":"Which HTML element is used to define the description Data?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<dt>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<li>","answer_d":"<dd>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":486,"question":"Which of the following is a declaration for an HTML document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>.....</html>","answer_b":"<p>.....</p>","answer_c":"<!DOCTYPE Html>","answer_d":"<body>.....</body>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":487,"question":"If you want to change the text color to red which of the following tags you'll use?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"< Body Text = Red>","answer_b":"< Body Colour = Red>","answer_c":"< Body Bgcolour = Red>","answer_d":"None Of These","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":488,"question":"HTML Uses","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Fixed Tags Defined By The Language","answer_b":"Pre-specified Tags","answer_c":"Tags Only For Linking","answer_d":"User Defined Tags","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":490,"question":"How are links defined in an <a> tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Href","answer_b":"Src-link","answer_c":"Src","answer_d":"Hlink","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":491,"question":"Which of the following is true about HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTML5 is the next major revision of the HTML standard superseding HTML 4.01, XHTML 1.0, and XHTML 1.1.","answer_b":"HTML5 is a cooperation between the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Web Hypertext Application Technology Working Group (WHATWG).","answer_c":"HTML5 is a standard for structuring and presenting content on the World Wide Web","answer_d":"All of These","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":492,"question":"Which of the following tags represents a section of the document intended for navigation in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"footer","answer_b":"dialog","answer_c":"section","answer_d":"nav","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":494,"question":"Which of the following is true about Cookies?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Cookies are limited to about 4 KB of data . Not enough to store required data.","answer_b":"Cookies are included with every HTTP request, thereby slowing down your web application by transmitting the same data.","answer_c":"Cookies are included with every HTTP request, thereby sending data unencrypted over the internet.","answer_d":"All of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":495,"question":"Which value of Socket.readyState atribute of WebSocket indicates that the connection has been closed or could not be opened?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"0","answer_b":"1","answer_c":"2","answer_d":"3","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":496,"question":"Which of the following is correct about geolocation api in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTML5 Geolocation API lets you share your location with your favorite web sites.","answer_b":"A Javascript can capture your latitude and longitude and can be sent to backend web server and do fancy location-aware things like finding local businesses or showing your location on a map.","answer_c":"Today most of the browsers and mobile devices support Geolocation API.","answer_d":"All of these","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":497,"question":"Which of the following attribute is used to group elements?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"item","answer_b":"itemgroup","answer_c":"itemcheck","answer_d":"itemprop","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":498,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers event after the document is printed?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"offlineprint","answer_b":"onbeforeprint","answer_c":"onafterprint","answer_d":"onprint","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":499,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when the length of the media is changed?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ondrop","answer_b":"onended","answer_c":"onemptied","answer_d":"ondurationchange","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":500,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers an event when media data is loaded?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"onhaschange","answer_b":"onloadeddata","answer_c":"onload","answer_d":"oninpu","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":501,"question":"Tags and text that are not directly displayed on the page are written in _____ section.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>","answer_b":"<body>","answer_c":"<title>","answer_d":"<head>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":502,"question":"Which tag inserts a line horizontally on your web page?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<hr>","answer_b":"<line direction=\"horizontal\">","answer_c":"<tr>","answer_d":"<line>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":503,"question":"Which tag allows you to add a row in a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<td> and </td>","answer_b":"<tr> and </tr>","answer_c":"<th> and </th>","answer_d":"<cr> and </cr>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":504,"question":"Which HTML tag would be used to display power in expression (A+B)2 ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<sup>","answer_b":"<p>","answer_c":"<b>","answer_d":"<sub>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":505,"question":"Which of the following is an attribute of the <Table> tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SRC","answer_b":"BOLD","answer_c":"CELLPADDING","answer_d":"LINK","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":506,"question":"Which of the following are commonly found in web pages?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"internet","answer_b":"hyperlinks","answer_c":"intranet","answer_d":"all of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":507,"question":"Which is not a domain name extension","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":".mil","answer_b":".com","answer_c":".int","answer_d":".org","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":508,"question":"A homepage is __________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"an index of encyclopedia articles","answer_b":"the first page of a website","answer_c":"required for access to the Internet","answer_d":"where all Internet data is stored","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":509,"question":"<TD> … </TD> tag is used for ________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Table heading","answer_b":"none of the above","answer_c":"Table row","answer_d":"Table Records","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":510,"question":"<SCRIPT> … </SCRIPT> tag can be placed within ________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Header","answer_b":"Body","answer_c":"Both the header and the body","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":511,"question":"Which tag is used to display the large font size?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<LARGE></LARGE>","answer_b":"<FONT></FONT>","answer_c":"< SIZE ></SIZE>","answer_d":"<BIG></BIG>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":512,"question":"Text within <EM> … </EM> tag is displayed as ________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"bold","answer_b":"indented","answer_c":"list","answer_d":"italic","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":513,"question":"Outlook Express is a _________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"E-Mail Client","answer_b":"Browser","answer_c":"SearchEngine","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":514,"question":"What is the full form of HTTP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Hyper text transfer package","answer_b":"Hyphenation text test program","answer_c":"Hyper text transfer protocol","answer_d":"none of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":515,"question":"Which of the following is not a pair tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<p>","answer_b":"<img>","answer_c":"<i>","answer_d":"< u >","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":516,"question":"To create a combo box (drop down box) which tag will you use?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<select>","answer_b":"<list>","answer_c":"<input type=\"dropdown\">","answer_d":"all of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":517,"question":"Which attribute is used to name an element uniquely?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"class","answer_b":"d","answer_c":"dot","answer_d":"all of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":518,"question":"What does vlink attribute mean?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"visited link","answer_b":"active link","answer_c":"very good link","answer_d":"virtual link","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":519,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a hyperlink?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<a href=\"http://mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz</a>","answer_b":"<http://mcqsets.com</a>","answer_c":"<a name=\"http://mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz</a>","answer_d":"url=\"http://mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":520,"question":"Tags and test that are not directly displayed on the page are written in _____ section.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>","answer_b":"<body>","answer_c":"<title>","answer_d":"<head>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":521,"question":"<b> tag makes the enclosed text bold. What is other tag to make text bold?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<strong>","answer_b":"<emp>","answer_c":"<black>","answer_d":"<dar>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":522,"question":"Which attribute you’ll use with the TD tag to merge two cells horizontally?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"merge=colspan2","answer_b":"merge=row2","answer_c":"colspan=2","answer_d":"rowspan=2","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":523,"question":"Which attribute can be used with BODY tag to set background color green?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"background=\"green\"","answer_b":"bgcolor=\"green\"","answer_c":"vlink=\"green\"","answer_d":"None of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":524,"question":"Which attribute is used with an img tag to display the text if image could not load in browser?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"description","answer_b":"id","answer_c":"alt","answer_d":"name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":525,"question":"Which of the following is not a valid alignment attribute?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Left","answer_b":"Top","answer_c":"Right","answer_d":"All of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":526,"question":"When would you use path along with file name of a picture in an IMG tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"path is optional and not necessary","answer_b":"when image file and html file both are on same location d.","answer_c":"path is always necessary when inserting image","answer_d":"when the location of image file and html file are different","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":527,"question":"HTML supports","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ordered lists","answer_b":"unordered lists","answer_c":"both type of lists","answer_d":"does not support those types","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":528,"question":"Which of the following is an attribute related to font tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"size","answer_b":"All the options are style tags","answer_c":"color","answer_d":"face","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":529,"question":"The way the browser displays the object can be modified by _____","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"attributes","answer_b":"modifiers","answer_c":"parameters","answer_d":"None of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":530,"question":"Which of the following is not a style tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<b>","answer_b":"All are style tags","answer_c":"<i>","answer_d":"<tt>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":531,"question":"To create a blank line in your web page","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"press Enter two times","answer_b":". insert <BLINE>","answer_c":"insert <BR> tag","answer_d":"press Shift + Enter","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":532,"question":"There are ____ different heading tags in HTML","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"4","answer_b":"7","answer_c":"6","answer_d":"5","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":533,"question":"In HTML document the tags","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Should be written in upper case","answer_b":"can be written in both uppercase or lowercase","answer_c":"should be written in propercase","answer_d":"should be written in lower case","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":534,"question":"The _____ character tells browsers to stop tagging the text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"?","answer_b":">","answer_c":"%","answer_d":"/","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":535,"question":"Some tags enclose the text. Those tags are known as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Couple tags","answer_b":"Pair tags","answer_c":"Double tags","answer_d":"Single tags","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":536,"question":"HTML documents are saved in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Special binary format","answer_b":"Machine language codes","answer_c":"ASCII text","answer_d":"None of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":537,"question":"Which tag creates a check box for a form in HTML?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<checkbox>","answer_b":"<input checkbox>","answer_c":"<input=checkbox>","answer_d":"<input type=\"checkbox\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":538,"question":"Choose the correct HTML tag for the smallest size heading?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<heading>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<h6>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":539,"question":"How can we define a Video Tag in HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<video src \"URL\"></video>","answer_b":"<video src=\"URL\"></video>","answer_c":"<video></video>","answer_d":"<video src:\"URL\"></video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":540,"question":"What is the use of Canvas element in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The canvas element is used to draw graphics by making use of CSS. It is defined with the <canvas> tag.","answer_b":"The canvas element is used to draw graphics by making use of JavaScript. It is defined with the <canvas> tag.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":541,"question":"What is the use of Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) is the part of the vector-based family of graphics. There are various forms of Raster-based graphics available that stores the color definition for each pixel in an array of data.","answer_b":"Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) is the part of the colored-based family of graphics. There are various forms of Raster-based graphics available that stores the design definition for each pixel in an array of data.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":542,"question":"Why do we need HTML5 Server-Sent Events?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Server-Sent Events (SSE) is a recent HTML5 specification in combination with the EventSource API designed for streaming updates.","answer_b":"Server-Sent Events (SSE) is a recent HTML5 specification in combination with the EventSource API designed for getting POST and GET request.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":543,"question":"What is cite tag in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<cite title\"value\">Some Text Here</cite>","answer_b":"<cite title:\"value\">Some Text Here</cite>","answer_c":"<cite title=\"value\">Some Text Here</cite>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":544,"question":"What is MathML in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The Mathematical Markup Language (MathML) is a markup language to show mathematical and scientific content on the Web.","answer_b":"The Memory Manipulation Language (MemoryML) is a markup language used to store content on the Web.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":548,"question":"Which of the following is used to add multiple line comments in PHP ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"//","answer_b":"/* */","answer_c":"{{ }}","answer_d":"{/ \\}","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":549,"question":"Is PHP case sensitive","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Depending on the PHP version either Yes and No","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":973,"question":"Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<javascript>","answer_b":"<script>","answer_c":"<js>","answer_d":"<scripting>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"},{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":974,"question":"What is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the HTML element below?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"#demo.innerHTML = \"Hello World!\";","answer_b":"document.getElementById(\"demo\").innerHTML = \"Hello World!\";","answer_c":"document.getElement(\"p\").innerHTML = \"Hello World!\";","answer_d":"document.getElementByName(\"p\").innerHTML = \"Hello World!\";","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":975,"question":"Where is the correct place to insert a JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The <head> section","answer_b":"The <body> section","answer_c":"The <footer>","answer_d":"Both the <head> section and the <body> section are correct","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":976,"question":"What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called \"xxx.js\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<script name=\"xxx.js\">","answer_b":"<script src=\"xxx.js\">","answer_c":"<script href=\"xxx.js\">","answer_d":"<script declare=\"xxx.js\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":977,"question":"The external JavaScript file must contain the <script> tag.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":978,"question":"How do you write \"Hello World\" in an alert box?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"msgBox(\"Hello World\");","answer_b":"alert(\"Hello World\");","answer_c":"msg(\"Hello World\");","answer_d":"alertBox(\"Hello World\");","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":979,"question":"How do you create a function in JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"function myFunction()","answer_b":"function:myFunction()","answer_c":"function = myFunction()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":980,"question":"How do you call a function named \"myFunction\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"myFunction()","answer_b":"call myFunction()","answer_c":"call function myFunction()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":981,"question":"How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"if i = 5 then","answer_b":"if i = 5","answer_c":"if i == 5 then","answer_d":"if (i == 5)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":982,"question":"How to write an IF statement for executing some code if \"i\" is NOT equal to 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"if (i != 5)","answer_b":"if (i <> 5)","answer_c":"if i =! 5 then","answer_d":"if i <> 5","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":983,"question":"How does a WHILE loop start?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"while (i <= 10)","answer_b":"while i = 1 to 10","answer_c":"while (i <= 10; i++)","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":984,"question":"How does a FOR loop start?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"for i = 1 to 5","answer_b":"for (i = 0; i <= 5; i++)","answer_c":"for (i <= 5; i++)","answer_d":"for (i = 0; i <= 5)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":985,"question":"How can you add a comment in a JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"//This is a comment","answer_b":"'This is a comment","answer_c":"<!--This is a comment-->","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":986,"question":"How to insert a comment that has more than one line?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"/*This comment has more than one line*/","answer_b":"<!--This comment has more than one line-->","answer_c":"//This comment has more than one line//","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":987,"question":"What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"var colors = 1 = (\"red\"), 2 = (\"green\"), 3 = (\"blue\")","answer_b":"var colors = \"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"","answer_c":"var colors = [\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"]","answer_d":"var colors = (1:\"red\", 2:\"green\", 3:\"blue\")","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":988,"question":"How do you round the number 7.25, to the nearest integer?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Math.round(7.25)","answer_b":"round(7.25)","answer_c":"rnd(7.25)","answer_d":"Math.rnd(7.25)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":989,"question":"How do you find the number with the highest value of x and y?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ceil(x, y)","answer_b":"Math.ceil(x, y)","answer_c":"Math.max(x, y)","answer_d":"top(x, y)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":990,"question":"What is the correct JavaScript syntax for opening a new window called \"w2\" ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"w2 = window.new(\"http://www.w3schools.com\");","answer_b":"w2 = window.open(\"http://www.w3schools.com\");","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":991,"question":"JavaScript is the same as Java.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":992,"question":"How can you detect the client's browser name?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"browser.name","answer_b":"navigator.appName","answer_c":"client.navName","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":993,"question":"Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"onchange","answer_b":"onmouseclick","answer_c":"onmouseover","answer_d":"onclick","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":994,"question":"How do you declare a JavaScript variable?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"v carName;","answer_b":"variable carName;","answer_c":"var carName;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":995,"question":"Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"x","answer_b":"-","answer_c":"=","answer_d":"*","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":996,"question":"What will the following code return: Boolean(10 > 9)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"true","answer_b":"NaN","answer_c":"false","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0},{"id":997,"question":"Is JavaScript case-sensitive?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy","successTally":0,"failureTally":0}]